Finding Aid for the Allegra Fuller Snyder papers, 1960-2010 LSC.1881
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research Materials and Organizations Files., 1960-2010
  - Los Angeles Festival-Looking Out., 1990-1993 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    Brochures, correspondence, newsclippings. "Looking Out: Critical imperatives in world dance" and "Hollywood Images of World Dance" by AFS.
  - Martin, Gyorgy., 1985 and undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
    Photocopies of articles "Monographie Internationale del la Danse Populaire," "Ethnic and Social Strata in the Naming of Dances," "A Structural Analysis of the Hungarian Folk Dance," "East-European Relations of Hungarian Dance Types."
  - Merriam, Alan P., 1972 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    Photocopy of CORD conference article "Anthropology and the Dance."
  - Music Center of Los Angeles County., 1975, 1989, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    Invitation to be a reader for the Bravo Awards. 2007 /2008 "Dance at the Music Center" program. 1975 "Rug Concert" flyer.
  - Naropa Institute., 1983-1986 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    Letters from the Colorado-based institute. Catalogs.
  - National Association of Regional Ballet (NARB)., 1971 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    Brochure. Spring 1971 "NARB Newsletter."
  - National Dance Guild (NDG)., 1967-1968 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    12th annual convention brochure and correspondence. See American Dance Guild (ADG) Box 65, folder 6.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)., 1968-1981 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    AFS as consultant wrote this 1968 report for NEA "The Relationship of Film to Dance: a report and analysis of problems, needs, possibilities and potentials in the area."
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Content Materials 1960s., 1960-1969 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    American Film Institute press releases announcing programs. 1967 - 1968 state programs funding for dance projects. Use of film and dance.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Content Materials 1960s Correspondence., 1960-1969 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Correspondence about film requests and the use of film and dance. Newsclippings about dance films.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Coordinated Residency Touring Program., 1970-1974 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Company data and descriptive sheets.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Correspondence 1963-1972. (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Correspondence with dance groups about their projects including Omega Community of the Arts, Huntington Performing Arts Foundation, New Dance Group Studio.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-The First Five Years., 1970 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    "National Council on the Arts, National Endowment for the Arts: The first five years: Fiscal 1966 through fiscal 1970."
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Manhattan Festival Ballet., 1969-1970 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    Manhattan Festival Ballet proposal Statement of purpose, budget, photocopies of newsclippings.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1969-1970. (Box 88, Folder 6)
    NEA Advisory panel agendas. Reports on proposals rejected and funded. Choreography commissions, dance programs allocations, budgets. Correspondence.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1970-1971. (Box 88, Folder 7)
    Dance Fellowship announcements with dollars. June Arey position paper on the dance panel. Performance budgets and schedules. Correspondence.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1971-1972. (Box 88, Folder 8)
    Projects recommended for year 1971 if funds are available. Residency Touring Program summary sheets season 1971-1972. All programs fiscal 1971. Correspondence.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1972-1973. (Box 89, Folder 1)
    NEA dance program announcement for fiscal 1972. Informational packets for Raymond Johnson, Sara Shelton, Gloria Newman Dance Theater, Dance Repertory Company.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1973-1974. (Box 89, Folder 2)
    NEA dance program announcement for fiscal 1973. Informational packets for "200 By the Bi," The Solomons Company, Cliff Keuter, Shelton-Johnson.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1981-1982. (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Correspondence among panel members, with performers and with performance organizations.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1982-1983. (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Memorandum. AFS site visit records. Choreography Fellowships fiscal 1983.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1985 (1 of 2). (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Packet of dance grant proposals and some AFS notes.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Panelist Information 1985 (2 of 2). (Box 89, Folder 6)
    Packet of dance grant proposals, continued.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Proposals 1969. (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Individual dance grant applications. Dance group applications.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Proposals 1970. (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Individual dance grant applications. Dance group, productions, and organizations applications.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Proposals 1971 (1 of 2). (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Individual dance grant applications. Dance group and organizations applications. Commissions lists.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Proposals 1971 (2 of 2). (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Project dance grant applications.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Relationship of Film to Dance (1 of 2)., 1968 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    AFS report for NEA on the relationship of film to dance outline and correspondence.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Relationship of Film to Dance (2 of 2)., 1968 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    AFS full report for NEA on the relationship of film to dance.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Relationship of Film to Dance Questionnaires (1 of 4)., 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Prototype letter and two-page Bulletin AFS conducted regarding the relationship of film to dance. Collected questionnaires.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Relationship of Film to Dance Questionnaires (2 of 4)., 1968 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Collected questionnaires.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Relationship of Film to Dance Questionnaires (3 of 4)., 1968 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Relationship of Film to Dance Questionnaires (4 of 4)., 1968 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Relationship of Film to Dance Questionnaires Filmmakers and Librarians., 1968 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Collected questionnaires from filmmakers and librarians.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Rowe, Roger., 1963 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    NEA application "The History and Philosophy of Kung-Fu" by Roger Rowe.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-AFS Grant Teaching Materials for Dance History., 1976-1977 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Final report for the Education Project Grant "A Compilation of Teaching Materials for Dance History." Application materials for the "History of Dance-Baroque to 20th century" and "Secular Masque." Correspondence.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-AFS Grant Pueblo, People and Performances (1 of 2)., 1979-1980 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, drawings. No application materials. Coordinating with the Los Angeles Bi-Centennial Committee (LA 200).
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-AFS Grant Pueblo, People and Performances (2 of 2)., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Complete grant application for "Pueblo, People and Performances: The role of dance in Los Angeles History." Coordinating with the Los Angeles Bi-Centennial Committee (LA 200).
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Applications 1976-1977. (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Two applications for AFS review and the fiscal 1977 grant list for the Division of Public Programs Museums and Historical Organizations Programs.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Applications 1981-1989. (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Evaluator correspondence for summer stipend and fellowship grants. No grant proposals. Fellowships for Independent Study and Research 1981-1982 list.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Dance Database Project., 1987-1989 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Correspondence about Elsie Dunin's Dance Database Project. Evaluators' comments about why it was denied.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Summer Applications 1979. (Box 92, Folder 7)
    NEH summer stipend applications and evaluator notes by AFS. Correspondence.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Asian Performing Arts 1979 (1 of 2). (Box 92, Folder 8)
    AFS CV. Historic timeline of Japanese dance forms. Asian performing arts, puppetry, and films bibliographies. "Introduction to Chinese and Japanese Drama" by Pat Enders. Correspondence.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Asian Performing Arts 1979 (2 of 2). (Box 93, Folder 1)
    NEH Summer Seminar application booklets. List of past Summer Seminars for College Teachers. Preliminary Narrative Report. Application cover sheet. Grant award notification.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Asian Performing Arts 1981 (1 of 2). (Box 93, Folder 2)
    Individual $2,500 College Teacher Stipend applications to participate in the Asian Performing Arts 1981 summer program at UCLA.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Asian Performing Arts 1981 (2 of 2). (Box 93, Folder 3)
    Correspondence and thank you notes.
  - Native American Publications., 1987-1990 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    Vol. 17 no. 1 1989, Vol. 18 no. 1 1990 "Americans Before Columbus;" fall 1987, spring and winter 1988, spring 1989 "NARF: Native American rights fund legal review;" autumn 1987, spring 1989 "Daybreak: Dedicated to the seventh generation;" spring 1988 "Indian Affairs;" Sept. / Oct. 1992 "Smithsonian Runner: A newsletter for Native Americans;" June 1987 "Talking Leaf."
  - Newspaper Clippings., 1959-1978 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    1959 "Northwest Leader" article about Eugene Loring. 1959 "New York Time Magazine" article about Etienne Decroux and Marcel Marceau. 1960 "New York Times" article about change to folkloric Egyptian dance during Gamal Abdel Nasser's time. 1978 "Durham Morning Herald" articles American Dance Festival. "Life Magazine" article about UCLA arts programs.
  - New York University Visiting Professor of Performing Studies., 1982-1983 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    Flyers for AFS lecture "Viewing Dance Through American Indian Eyes." Tisch School of the Arts faculty meeting. Correspondence about AFS doing a one-year visiting professor position in performing studies.
  - Nikolais/Louis Foundation for Dance., 1993-1994 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Description of video documentation project. Correspondence. Photocopies of newsclippings. 1993 Occidental College performance program.
  - Non-Western Culture Schools Proposal., 1977-1979 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    "Non-Western Culture (Africa and Japan) Schools Proposal" by Elisabeth Babuscio.
  - Omega Institute., 1986-1987 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    Correspondence. "Omega Institute for Holistic Studies Summer 1986" catalog.
  - Pacific Asia Museum-Advisory Council., 1979-1981 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    Nov.-Dec. 1981 newsletter. AFS CV.
  - Pacific Rim Performing Arts Festival., 1988-1990 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    Planning Conference agenda. "1990 Pacific Rim Arts Festival Summary Report." Meeting notes.
  - Pamanlahi-de los Reyes., undated (Box 94, Folder 6)
    Booklet of Pamanlahi Philippine Dance Troupe directed by O'Nil Pineda de los Reyes.
  - Parabola., 1988 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    Summer "Parabola: The magazine of myth and tradition."
  - Performing Arts Council-Los Angeles Music Center., 1968-1970 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    "Music Center Arts & Education Fund" booklet. Correspondence and newsclippings.
  - Performing Arts Workshop (PAW)., 1966-1968 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    Correspondence about AFS doing a lecture or series at PAW in San Francisco.
  - Pike, Kenneth., 1954 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    Photocopy of chapter by Pike entitled "Emic and Etic Standpoints for the Description of Behavior."
  - Plato Society., 1981-1982 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    Correspondence about AFS speaking at the Plato Society at UCLA Colloquium. Brochure.
  - Postage Stamps., 2003 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    Eight plates of 20 U.S. 37 cent postage stamps of Martha Graham, Alvin Ailey, Agnes de Mille, and George Balanchine.
  - Postal, Susan Koessler., undated (Box 94, Folder 13)
    Photocopy of "Body-Image and Identity: A comparison of Kwakiutl and Hopi."
  - Research Material and Notes 1970s (I of 2)., 1970-1979 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    Dec. 24, 1973 "Newsweek Special Issue: The arts in America." "New Heaven and Earth" by Joyce Carol Oates. Brochures, newsletters, correspondence, newsclippings, articles used by AFS for research.
  - Research Material and Notes 1970s (2 of 2)., 1970-1979 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    Oct. 1972 "Intellectual Digest." Summer 1971 "Modern Dance" in Japanese. Brochures, newsletters, correspondence, newsclippings, articles used by AFS for research.
  - Research Material and Notes 1980s., 1980-1989 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    Brochures, newsletters, correspondence, newsclippings, articles used by AFS for research.
  - Retirement., 1991-1992 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    Letters of congratulations from Alma Hawkins, Chancellor Young, and the Dance Department community.
  - Royce, Anya Peterson., 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    "Social and Political Aspects of Dance Performance in Plural Societies."
  - Sabbaticals., 1982-1984 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    "Report on Sabbatical Leave, Academic Year 1983-84" which describes AFS Fulbright work at University of Surrey. Some correspondence during AFS 1982-1983 visiting professorship at NYU.
  - Schools for Alexandra., 1964-1970 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    Brochures, applications, letters of schools AFS researched for her daughter's education.
  - Shamanism Research and Notes-1970s to 1990s., 1994 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    Correspondence and postcards. International Society for Shamanistic Research 1994 newsletter and conference notice. Photocopies of notes on Finno-Ugrian practices and Carnavale practices. Paper entitled "Jonkanoo (John Canoe): An Afro- Jamaican Christmas festival." March 1993 "Anthropology of Consciousness." Photocopies of articles.
  - Shruti Newsletter., 1979-1980 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    March/April 1979-May/June 1980 newsletters.
  - Singer, Alice., 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    "Prolegomena to a Theory of Dance: Macedonian metrics, a first approximation," "Holiday Dancing in a Greek-Macedonian Village: Meaning in the movement," "Metrical Structure of Macedonian Dance," "Dance Movement in Macedonia as an Educational Tool for Understanding Expression in Culture."
  - Skating Club of New York., 1965-1971 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    1965, 1967, 1968, 1970-71 booklets of bylaws and membership lists.
  - Snoopy Dancing Banner., 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    Yellow felt banner of Snoopy dancing with the caption "To dance is to live, to live is to dance!" This was on AFS's dance department bulletin board.
  - Snoopy Dance Sweatshirt., 1967 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    Pink sleeveless sweatshirt of Snoopy dancing with the caption "To dance is to live, to live is to dance!"
  - Snyder, Robert., 1982 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    May 9 Los Angeles Herald Examiner: California Living article "An Artful Compromise: A Los Angeles parable of one couple, two creative temperaments and the clash of out-of-sync successes."
  - Society for the Anthropological Study of Human Movement (SASHM)., 1983 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Regarding AFS SASHM seminar presentation at NYU.
  - Society for the Anthropology of Visual Communication (SAVICOM)., 1980-1981 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    SAVICOM newsletters.
  - Society for Applied Anthropology., 1980 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    Preliminary program for the 40th annual meeting.
  - Society for Ethnomusicology (SEM)., 1974-1982 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    1974 and 1982 annual meeting brochures. "Twenty-Five Years: Coming of age abstracts." 1977 paper "Between the Event and the Tradition: A new look at music in sociocultural systems" by John E. Kaemmer.
  - Society for Ethnomusicology (SEM)-Michigan Conference., 1987 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    37th annual meeting brochure. "Thirty-Second Annual Meeting: Abstracts." AFS session presentation "Some Contributions of Gertrude Prokosch Kurath to Dance Ethnology."
  - Society for Ethnomusicology (SEM)-Newsletters., 1975-1986 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    March/April, Sept./Oct., Nov./Dec. 1975; July/Oct., Nov./Dec. 1976; Jan./Feb. 1977; Jan./Feb., May/June, July/Oct., Nov. 1978; Dec.78/Jan., Feb./March, April/May, June/Sept., Oct./Nov. 1979; Jan./April, May/Aug., Sept./Dec. 1980; Jan., May, Sept. 1981; Jan., May 1982; Sept. 1986.
  - Society for General Systems Research (SGSR)., 1984-1985 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    Society for General Systems Research program for 29th annual meeting.
  - Society for Humanistic Anthropology., 1981 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    March and May Society for Humanistic Anthropology Newsletters.
  - Southwest Museum-Los Angeles., 1988-1989 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Winter and spring 1989 "Anthropology of the Americas Masterkey." May/Aug. 1988 and Jan./ April 1989 "Southwest Museum News."
  - State University College at Buffalo., 1981-1983 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Correspondence regarding AFS evaluation of the dance department. Annual Report 1981-1982 supplemental items.
  - Student Projects., 1966-1985 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Papers, letters, programs that include students. "Murray Louis' New Film Series: Dance as an art form" correspondence.
  - Student Projects-Padfield (1 of 2)., 1990-1991 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    Letter about Marsha Lou Padfield graduating with PhD in dance ethnology from Union Institute. AFS was on her committee. "Interaction of Belief System and Nonverbal Communication: An examination of the type and function of movement in the Anglican church."
  - Student Projects-Padfield (2 of 2)., 1986-1989 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    "Learning Agreement Between Union Graduate School and Marsha Padfield." List of Union Graduate School faculty.
  - Student Projects-Snowden., 1972? (Box 98, Folder 1)
    "The Significance of Sensory Perception of Space to Body Image with Implications for Interrelationships and Movement Therapy" and the in-progress chapters of the master's thesis of Marianne Snowden.
  - Symbols Audio Cassette., undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
    An audio cassette entitled "Fuller on Symbols."
  - Taniguchi Symposium (1 of 3)., 1987-1990 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Publication correspondence. AFS lecture for Eleventh International Taniguchi Foundation Symposium "Levels of Gesture in the Dance Event." Transcription of dialog. One large group photo, 4 small borderless photos, 4 small with border color photos. 13 original indian ink dance illustrations.
  - Taniguchi Symposium (2 of 3)., 1987 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Participant handbook for the division of Ethnology "Gestures in Social Context."
  - Taniguchi Symposium (3 of 3)., 1987 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Drafts of presentations "Levels of Gesture in the Dance Event" by AFS, "External Influences in the Transformation of Japanese Dance" by Takane Hirai, "High-Collar Decorum: The conflict of manners between two civilization" by Masaichi Nomura, "The Foot in Japanese Culture" by Masao Yamaguchi.
  - Taniguchi Symposium-Yamaguchi publications., 1987 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Four publications by Masao Yamaguchi.
  - Taper Forum., 1968 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    Script for "The Adventures of the Black Girl in Her Search for God" by George Bernard Shaw adapted for stage by Christopher Isherwood for the Center Theatre Group.
  - Teatro Internacional., 1974-1979 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    "1976 Photo Recap." Jan. 1974 Newsletter. 1974, 1977, 1978, 1979 Annual Meeting Summaries.
  - Temple University-Graduate Dance Review., 1981 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    Vol. 1, No. 1 "Graduate Dance Review."
  - Tewa Indians of New Mexico-AFS Writings (1 of 2)., 1965 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    "An Analysis of the Cultural Content of the Tewa Tales" by AFS.
  - Tewa Indians of New Mexico-AFS Writings (2 of 2)., undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
    Introduction and tabbed chapters written by AFS about Tewa practices and referenced materials.
  - Tewa Indians of New Mexico-Note Cards (1 of 2)., undated (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Two packages of file cards with notes and references.
  - Tewa Indians of New Mexico-Note Cards (2 of 2)., undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
    Two bundles of file cards with notes and references.
  - Tewa Indians of New Mexico-Correspondence., 1958-1965 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    "Music of the Pueblos Apache and Navajo" and "Masks, Mantas, and Moccasins: Dance costumes of the Pueblo Indians" both brochures published by the Taylor Museum of the Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center. "Game Animal Dances of the Rio Grande Pueblos" by Gertrude Prokosch Kurath. Correspondence.
  - Twyla Tharp Residency., 1971-1972 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Outreach notice from Alma Hawkins about the dance happening that will be overseen by Twyla Tharp. Two 8x10 b/w photos of Tharp.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 50., 1979 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    Course outline.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 140 Dance and Culture., 1980-1989 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    Course outlines, handouts, bibliographies. See Box 101, folder 5 UCLA Course Material-Dance 187.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 140 Dance and Culture Readings., 1976-1980 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    Syllabus material. "Sources on African and African-Related Dance" compiled by Thompson Drewal and Jackson. "The Kambari People and Their Dances" by Harper.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 141 Lighting for Dance., 1987-1990 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    1987 and 1990 "Lighting Showcase" programs.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 142 Dance of the Balkans., 1971 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    Bibliography for course taught by Elsie Dunin. Bulgarian terms sheet. Dance zones of Bulgaria sheet.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 151 History of Dance., 1969-1971 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    Course descriptions of course taught by Juana de Laban.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 158 Philosophical Bases and Trends in Dance (1 of 2)., 1967-1980 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Course outlines, handouts, bibliographies. Survey answers of student familiarity with reknown dancers and films about dance. "Two Ways of Knowing" handout.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 158 Philosophical Bases and Trends in Dance (2 of 2)., 1980 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    Course outlines, handouts, bibliographies of course taught by Pia Gilbert. Dance journal of Marlene Therkelsen.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 161/261 Ritual and Transformation., 1994 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    Course description taught by Irma Dosamantes Beaudry.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 182., 1984 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    Readings related to some dance forms South of Saharan Africa. "The Dance of the Bedu Moon" by Drid Williams. "Bete Masked Dance: A view from within" by Armistead Rood. "Gelede Dance of the Western Yoruba" by Thompson Drewal and Drewal.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 187/287 Dance Cultures of Native American Indians., 1991 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    Syllabus, handouts. "The Dance Symbol" paper presented by AFS at CORD conference.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 197/297 Ways of Knowing and Not Knowing., 1994 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    "Ways of Knowing and Not Knowing: Exploring Conceptual Frames Through Forms of Ritual and Modes of Healing: A cross-cultural and comparative inquiry" course description. Student class project proposals.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 202 Research Methods and Bibliography in Dance., 1964 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    Selected reference materials list for course.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 210 Aesthetics for Dance., 1973 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    Undated course description and syllabus.
  - UCLA Course Material-Dance 226 Dance Ethnology., 1967-1978 (Box 101, Folder 9)